A Guide to the Policy Office Legislative Files of Governor James S. Gilmore, 1998-2001
Library of Virginia
- HB 1878 (99) Public Recreational Facilities Authorities (Box 18, Folder 88)
- HB 1879 (99) Banking and Finance; Registered Check Cashers (Box 18, Folder 89)
- HB 1880 (99) Wireless Enhanced Public Safety Telephone Act (Box 18, Folder 90)
- HB 1881 (99) Public Service Corporations and Electric Authorities; Eminent Domain (Box 18, Folder 91)
- HB 1885 (99) DMV Agencies (Box 18, Folder 92)
- HB 1886 (99) Board for Contractors, Tradesman; Unlicensed Activity; Penalty (Box 18, Folder 93)
- HB 1886 (99) Income Tax; Voluntary Contribution to US Olympic Committee (Box 18, Folder 94)
- HB 1888 (99) Ann Goode Cooper Highway (Box 18, Folder 95)
- HB 1890 (99) Board for Contractors; Exemptions from Licensure (Box 18, Folder 96)
- HB 1891 (99) ABC; Definitions (Box 18, Folder 97)
- HB 1892 (99) Health Professions; Opticians (Box 18, Folder 98)
- HB 1893 (99) Comp. Comm. Corrections Act for Local-Responsible Offenders (Box 18, Folder 99)
- HB 1894 (99) School Board Regulation of Laser Pointer Use (Box 18, Folder 100)
- HB 1895 (99) Information About the Teaching Profession (Box 18, Folder 101)
- HB 1896 (99) Use of Term "Imitation Controlled Substance" (Box 18, Folder 102)
- HB 1899 (99) Permissible Venue (Box 18, Folder 103)
- HB 1901 (99) Uninsured Motorist Coverage; John Doe Actions (Box 18, Folder 104)
- HB 1902 (99) Bailees' Liens and Mechanics' Liens, Amounts (Box 18, Folder 105)
- HB 1905 (99) Secretary of the Commonwealth; Information on General Assembly Members (Box 18, Folder 106)
- HB 1906 (99) Local Regulation of Animals (Box 19, Folder 1)
- HB 1911 (99) Leased Personal Property (Box 19, Folder 2)
- HB 1913 (99) Charitable Gaming; Prohibited Practices (Box 19, Folder 3)
- HB 1915 (99) Code Commission; Title Revisions (Box 19, Folder 4)
- HB 1916 (99) Highway Signs (Box 19, Folder 5)
- HB 1917 (99) Motor Vehicle Dealers (Box 19, Folder 6)
- HB 1921 (99) Coalbed Methane; Pooling Orders (Box 19, Folder 7)
- HB 1922 (99) Structured Settlements; Authorization for Transfer (Box 19, Folder 8)
- HB 1925 (99) Annual School Board Reports (Box 19, Folder 9)
- HB 1928 (99) Health; Vital Statistics (Box 19, Folder 10)
- HB 1930 (99) BPOL Tax; License Tax on Motor Vehicle Dealers (Box 19, Folder 11)
- HB 1933 (99) Income Tax Deduction for Purchase of Prepaid Tuition Contracts (Box 19, Folder 12)
- HB 1934 (99) Road Tax; Credit for Payment of Motor Fuel, Diesel Fuel, etc. Tax (Box 19, Folder 13)
- HB 1935 (99) Public Procurement Act; Exemptions (Box 19, Folder 14)
- HB 1936 (99) Accident and Sickness Insurance; Group Policies, etc. (Box 19, Folder 15)
- HB 1937 (99) Public Utilities; Persons Not Designated as Public Utility, etc. (Box 19, Folder 16)
- HB 1938 (99) Certificate of Authority of a Savings Association to Do Business (Box 19, Folder 17)
- HB 1940 (99) Christopher Newport University; Electronic Commerce (Box 19, Folder 18)
- HB 1941 (99) Corrections of Local Taxes (Box 19, Folder 19)
- HB 1942 (99) Local Revenue Collection Procedures (Box 19, Folder 20)
- HB 1944 (99) Personal Property Tax; Book Produced by Electronic Means (Box 19, Folder 21)
- HB 1945 (99) Funeral Expenses (Box 19, Folder 22)
- HB 1946 (99) Vouchers and Statement of Assets on Hand (Box 19, Folder 23)
- HB 1949 (99) Finance Charges Under Closed-End Installment Plans (Box 19, Folder 24)
- HB 1951 (99) Permitting Prisoners to Work on Public, etc. Projects (Box 19, Folder 25)
- HB 1953 (99) Enterprise Zone Designations (Box 19, Folder 26)
- HB 1958 (99) Prescriptive Authority of Licensed Nurse Practitioners (Box 19, Folder 27)
- HB 1959 (99) Election Law Offenses; Filings of Complaints with Attorney for the Commonwealth (Box 19, Folder 28)
- HB 1960 (99) Laser Speed "Guns" (Box 19, Folder 29)
- HB 1961 (99) Absentee Ballots; Return of Unused Ballots, Replacement Ballots (Box 19, Folder 30)
- HB 1962 (99) Vacant Buildings; Registration (Box 19, Folder 31)
- HB 1963 (99) Residence Requirements for Certain Local Employees (Box 19, Folder 32)
- HB 1964 (99) Uniform Statewide Building Code; Violations (Box 19, Folder 33)
- HB 1965 (99) Liens for Water and Sewer Charges (Box 19, Folder 34)
- HB 1968 (99) Regulation of Personal Watercraft Rentals (Box 19, Folder 35)
- HB 1970 (99) Workers' Compensation; Presumption as to Death or Disability, Game Wardens (Box 19, Folder 36)
- HB 1971 (99) Window Films (Box 19, Folder 37)
- HB 1972 (99) Optometry; Revocation, Suspension, etc., of License (Box 19, Folder 38)
- HB 1974 (99) Health Professions; Volunteers (Box 19, Folder 39)
- HB 1975 (99) Employment of Instructional Personnel for Certain Courses (Box 19, Folder 40)
- HB 1976 (99) Health Professions; Substance Abuse Practitioners (Box 19, Folder 41)
- HB 1977 (99) Distribution of Proceeds of Tax Sales on Real Estate (Box 19, Folder 42)
- HB 1982 (99) Humane Investigators (Box 19, Folder 43)
- HB 1985 (99) Freedom of Information (Box 19, Folder 44)
- HB 1987 (99) Commonwealth's Surplus Motor Vehicles; Welfare Reform (Box 19, Folder 45)
- HB 1990 (99) Public Procurement Act; Exemptions (Box 19, Folder 46)
- HB 1992 (99) Child Care; Records Checks, Penalty (Box 19, Folder 47)
- HB 1993 (99) Salvage Dealers (Box 19, Folder 48)
- HB 1994 (99) Removal of Certain Signs (Box 19, Folder 49)
- HB 1995 (99) Electronic Security Equipment Definition (Box 19, Folder 50)
- HB 1996 (99) Wills, Estates, and Trusts; Pour-Over Wills (Box 19, Folder 51)
- HB 1997 (99) Tenants by the Entireties (Box 19, Folder 52)
- HB 1998 (99) Wills, Estates, and Trusts (Box 19, Folder 53)
- HB 1999 (99) Wills, Estates, and Trusts (Box 19, Folder 54)
- HB 2000 (99) Augmented Estate; Exclusions; Valuation (Box 19, Folder 55)
- HB 2001 (99) Duties of Attorneys-in-Fact and Agents Empowered Under Section 11-9.1 (Box 19, Folder 56)
- HB 2004 (99) Recapture of Nursing Home Depreciation (Box 19, Folder 57)
- HB 2008 (99) Definition of Child in Need of Supervision (Box 19, Folder 58)
- HB 2010 (99) Campaign Finance Disclosure Reports; Electronic Filings (Box 19, Folder 59)
- HB 2012 (99) Willfully Discharging Firearms in Public Places (Box 19, Folder 60)
- HB 2013 (99) Electronic Cooperatives; Purpose; Prohibited Activities (Box 19, Folder 61)
- HB 2014 (99) Petroleum Storage Tank Fund; Fees (Box 19, Folder 62)
- HB 2016 (99) Manufactured Homes (Box 19, Folder 63)
- HB 2023 (99) Volunteer Firefighters' and Rescue Squad Workers' Pension Fund (Box 19, Folder 64)
- HB 2026 (99) Spot Blight Abatement (Box 19, Folder 65)
- HB 2032 (99) Laser Speed "Guns" (Box 19, Folder 66)
- HB 2033 (99) Definition of Family Abuse (Box 19, Folder 67)
- HB 2034 (99) Intake; Petition; Investigation (Box 19, Folder 68)
- HB 2035 (99) Special Police Officers (Box 19, Folder 69)
- HB 2036 (99) Appointment of General Receivers; Their Duties; Audit of Funds (Box 19, Folder 70)
- HB 2039 (99) Speed Limit in Residence District (Box 19, Folder 71)
- HB 2041 (99) Crimes; Concealed Weapons (Box 19, Folder 72)
- HB 2043 (99) Juvenile Competency (Box 19, Folder 73)
- HB 2047 (99) Income Tax; State Forests Check-Off (Box 19, Folder 74)
- HB 2048 (99) Passing and Overtaking Vehicles (Box 19, Folder 75)
- HB 2050 (99) Towing (Box 19, Folder 76)
- HB 2054 (99) Executive Sedan Carriers and Limousine Carriers (Box 19, Folder 77)
- HB 2056 (99) Regulations for Remediation Programs (Box 19, Folder 78)
- HB 2057 (99) Flags for Service in National Guard (Box 19, Folder 79)
- HB 2058 (99) Close-Circuit TV Testimony of Child Victims (Box 19)
- HB 2061 (99) Board of Medicine; Practice of Acupuncture (Box 19, Folder 81)
- HB 2062 (99) Tax on Merchants (Box 19, Folder 82)
- HB 2064 (99) School Board Salaries (Box 19, Folder 83)
- HB 2067 (99) Workers' Compensation; Duty to Furnish Medical Attention (Box 19, Folder 84)
- HB 2073 (99) Definition of Construction, Highway and Increased Capacity (Box 19, Folder 85)
- HB 2074 (99) Banking and Finance; Joint Accounts, Required Disclosures (Box 19, Folder 86)
- HB 2075 (99) Comprehensive Services Act; CPMT (Box 19, Folder 87)
- HB 2076 (99) Salaries of Substitute Judges (Folder 88)
- HB 2077 (99) School Report Cards (Box 19, Folder 89)
- HB 2080 (99) Medical Care Facilities Certificate of Public Need (Box 19, Folder 90)
- HB 2081 (99) Department of Forestry (Box 20, Folder 1)
- HB 2085 (99) Local Business Taxes; Appeals (Box 20, Folder 2)
- HB 2086 (99) Transient Occupancy Tax; Prince William County (Box 20, Folder 3)
- HB 2088 (99) US Route 58 Virginia Transportation Revenue Bond Act of 1999 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- HB 2087 (99) National Teacher Certification Incentive Reward Program (Box 20, Folder 5)
- HB 2091 (99) Purchase of Handguns of Certain Officers (Box 20, Folder 6)
- HB 2092 (99) Local Taxation of Personal Property of Public Service Corporations (Box 20, Folder 7)
- HB 2095 (99) Clyde Boling Bridges (Box 20, Folder 8)
- HB 2096 (99) Virginia Regional Industrial Facilities Act (Box 20, Folder 9)
- HB 2097 (99) Automatic External Defibulators (Box 20, Folder 10)
- HB 2104 (99) Uniform Commercial Code; Financing Statements; Electronic Filings (Box 20, Folder 11)
- HB 2106 (99) BPOL Tax; Out-of-State Contractors (Box 20, Folder 12)
- HB 2107 (99) Consent by Minors (Box 20, Folder 13)
- HB 2110 (99) Street Names (Box 20, Folder 14)
- HB 2111 (99) Minutes of Meetings for Counties (Box 20, Folder 15)
- HB 2114 (99) Exhumation of Corpses (Box 20, Folder 16)
- HB 2122 (99) Standards of Quality (Box 20, Folder 17)
- HB 2124 (99) Sale of Bear (Box 20)
- HB 2125 (99) Wild Game Licenses (Box 20, Folder 19)
- HB 2126 (99) Telephone Sale of Game Licenses (Box 20, Folder 20)
- HB 2127 (99) Unemployment Compensation and Trust Fund Commission (Box 20, Folder 21)
- HB 2128 (99) Child Fatality Review (Box 20, Folder 22)
- HB 2130 (99) Unemployment Compensation; Tax Rates for New Employees (Box 20, Folder 23)
- HB 2131 (99) Workers' Compensation; Furnishing Copy of Medical Report (Box 20, Folder 24)
- HB 2132 (99) Workers' Compensation; Failure to Pay Compensation; Good Cause (Box 20, Folder 25)
- HB 2136 (99) Taxable Real Estate; Exemptions for Elderly and Disabled (Box 20, Folder 26)
- HB 2138 (99) Design-Build/Construction Management Review Board; Members (Box 20, Folder 27)
- HB 2139 (99) VDOT Projects (Box 20, Folder 28)
- HB 2141 (99) Computation of Daily Membership for Half-Day Kindergarten Programs (Box 20, Folder 29)
- HB 2144 (99) Student Expulsions for Drug Offenses (Box 20, Folder 30)
- HB 2146 (99) Fiduciaries (Box 20, Folder 31)
- HB 2148 (99) Professional Solicitors (Box 20, Folder 32)
- HB 2152 (99) Privacy Protection Act; Definitions (Box 20, Folder 33)
- HB 2153 (99) New Year's Day 2000 (Box 20, Folder 34)
- HB 2154 (99) Taxation; Failure to Pay Certain Local Taxes (Box 20, Folder 35)
- HB 2155 (99) Confinement and Disposition of Stray Animals (Box 20, Folder 36)
- HB 2157 (99) Laser Speed "Guns" (Box 20, Folder 37)
- HB 2158 (99) Tort Claims Act; "Year 2000" Immunity for Constitutional Officers (Box 20, Folder 38)
- HB 2159 (99) Substance Abuse Screening of Certain Offenders (Box 20, Folder 39)
- HB 2164 (99) Board for Contractors; Contractor Transaction Recovery Fund (Box 20, Folder 40)
- HB 2169 (99) Bond Authorization for Kiptopeake State Park Facility (Box 20, Folder 41)
- HB 2170 (99) Ignition Interlock Systems; Penalty (Box 20, Folder 42)
- HB 2171 (99) Sheriffs and Deputies in Buchanan County (Box 20, Folder 43)
- HB 2176 (99) Public School Foundations (Box 20, Folder 44)
- HB 2177 (99) Industrial Development and Revenue Bond Act (Box 20, Folder 45)
- HB 2178 (99) Department of Environment Quality Enforcement (Box 20, Folder 46)
- HB 2185 (99) Family Violence (Box 20, Folder 47)
- HB 2188 (99) Secretary of Technology Created (Box 20, Folder 48)
- HB 2189 (99) Undergraduate and Vocational Incentive Program (Box 20, Folder 49)
- HB 2190 (99) State Lottery Law; Gamblers Anonymous (Box 20, Folder 50)
- HB 2191 (99) Administrative Process Act; Exemptions and Exclusions (Box 20, Folder 51)
- HB 2193 (99) Tax Credit for Care Provided to Impaired Elderly Relatives (Box 20, Folder 52)
- HB 2195 (99) Commonwealth Transportation Board; Membership (Box 20, Folder 53)
- HB 2196 (99) Fees Collected by Clerks of the Circuit Courts (Box 20, Folder 54)
- HB 2200 (99) Virginia Education Coordinating Council (Box 20, Folder 55)
- HB 2201 (99) Persons Eligible to Serve on School Boards (Box 20, Folder 56)
- HB 2204 (99) HOV Lanes in Tidewater Virginia (Box 20, Folder 57)
- HB 2205 (99) Preschool of Nursery School Programs; Exempt from Licensure (Box 20, Folder 58)
- HB 2206 (99) Childhood Immunizations (Box 20, Folder 59)
- HB 2209 (99) Trucks Hauling Gravel, Sand or Crushed Stone (Box 20, Folder 60)
- HB 2210 (99) Coal Mine Safety Act (Box 20, Folder 61)
- HB 2211 (99) Local Tax Administration; Sale of Land for Delinquent Taxes (Box 20, Folder 62)
- HB 2213 (99) Health Insurance; Fair Business Practices (Box 20, Folder 63)
- HB 2217 (99) Hunting with Firearms While Under Influence (Box 20, Folder 64)
- HB 2219 (99) Vacancies in Local Governing Body, Elected School Boards, etc. (Box 20, Folder 65)
- HB 2220 (99) Regulating Mooring and Anchoring (Box 20, Folder 66)
- HB 2221 (99) Removal of Property from Waters, Penalty (Box 20, Folder 67)
- HB 2222 (99) Insurance; Payment and Sharing Commissions, Trade Names (Box 20, Folder 68)
- HB 2223 (99) Individual Income Tax; Credit for Taxes Paid Other States (Box 20, Folder 69)
- HB 2228 (99) Health Regulation; Nursing Homes and Certified Nursing Aids (Box 20, Folder 70)
- HB 2229 (99) State Purchasing Contracts; Charitable Corporations (Box 20, Folder 71)
- HB 2230 (99) Virginia Children's Medical Security Insurance Plan (Box 20, Folder 72)
- HB 2231 (99) Local Taxes; Deeding Title of Certain Real Estate to Locality (Box 20, Folder 73)
- HB 2233 (99) Virginia Export Loan Guarantee Fund (Box 20, Folder 74)
- HB 2236 (99) Encryption Used in Criminal Activity; Penalty (Box 2, Folder 75)
- HB 2238 (99) Town Street Standards (Box 20, Folder 76)
- HB 2241 (99) Public School Educational Technology Grants Program and Fund (Box 20, Folder 77)
- HB 2242 (99) Water Supply Assistance Grant Fund (Box 20, Folder 78)
- HB 2245 (99) Department of Veteran's Affairs; Hiring Preference for Veterans (Box 20, Folder 79)
- HB 2246 (99) Real Estate Appraiser Board; Membership (Box 20, Folder 80)
- HB 2248 (99) Alcoholic Beverage Control; Adoption of Regulations (Box 20, Folder 81)
- HB 2249 (99) Regulations of the ABC Board; Credit Card Purchases by Licensees (Box 20, Folder 82)
- HB 2250 (99) Bank Branches; Establishment (Box 20, Folder 83)
- HB 2251 (99) Multistate Trust Institutions (Box 20, Folder 84)
- HB 2252 (99) Law-Enforcement Expenditures (Box 20, Folder 85)
- HB 2254 (99) Embezzlement of Court-Ordered Child Support (Box 20, Folder 86)
- HB 2255 (99) Selective Service Compliance (Box 20, Folder 87)
- HB 2256 (99) Workers' Compensation; Capitol Police Officers (Box 20, Folder 88)
- HB 2259 (99) Child Welfare Agencies (Box 20, Folder 89)
- HB 2263 (99) Teacher Licensure; Technology Proficiency (Box 20, Folder 90)
- HB 2265 (99) Labor and Employment; Governmental Employee Associations (Box 20, Folder 91)
- HB 2266 (99) Submerged Aquatic Vegetation (Box 20, Folder 92)
- HB 2267 (99) Tributary Plans; Sediments and Suspended Solids (Box 20, Folder 93)
- HB 2268 (99) Suspended Solids; Water Quality Improvement Act Grants (Box 20, Folder 94)
- HB 2269 (99) Public Trust in Subaqueous Lands (Box 20, Folder 95)
- HB 2271 (99) Workers' Compensation; Suspension of Award Pending Appeal (Box 20, Folder 96)
- HB 2272 (99) Impact of Piers on Oyster Grounds (Box 20, Folder 97)
- HB 2274 (99) Senior Citizens Higher Education Act (Box 20, Folder 98)
- HB 2276 (99) Residential Landlord and Tenant Act; Rent Escrow Required (Box 20, Folder 99)
- HB 2277 (99) Local Telecommunications Services (Box 20, Folder 100)
- HB 2278 (99) Riverside Regional Jail Authority (Box 20, Folder 101)
- HB 2279 (99) Crab and Peeler Pots (Box 20, Folder 102)
- HB 2280 (99) Board for Contractors; Natural Gas (Box 20, Folder 103)
- HB 2281 (99) Drug Control; Scheduling (Box 21, Folder 1)
- HB 2283 (99) Guaranteed Availability of Individual Health Insurance Coverage (Box 21, Folder 2)
- HB 2290 (99) Neighborhood Assistance Act; Donation of Professional Services (Box 21, Folder 3)
- HB 2292 (99) Private Pleasure Watercraft; Optional Uninsured Coverage (Box 21, Folder 4)
- HB 2294 (99) Habitual Offender License Reissuance (Box 21, Folder 5)
- HB 2295 (99) Childhood Immunizations (Box 21, Folder 6)
- HB 2296 (99) Driving While Intoxicated (Box 21, Folder 7)
- HB 2297 (99) Notice of Judicial Vacancies (Box 21, Folder 8)
- HB 2299 (99) Appeal of Virginia Employment Commission Decisions (Box 21, Folder 9)
- HB 2302 (99) Virginia Residential Landlord and Tenant Act; Tenants' Obligationsi (Box 21, Folder 10)
- HB 2303 (99) Secondary Roads, "Pave-in-Place" Program (Box 21, Folder 11)
- HB 2306 (99) Marine Resources Commission Member Qualifications (Box 21, Folder 12)
- HB 2307 (99) Insurance; Unfair Settlement Practices; Replacement and Repair (Box 21, Folder 13)
- HB 2311 (99) Unemployment Compensation; Disqualification for Benefits; Misconduct (Box 21, Folder 14)
- HB 2312 (99) Certification of Value of Qualifying Vehicles (Box 21, Folder 15)
- HB 2313 (99) Correction Erroneous Real Estate Assessments (Box 21, Folder 16)
- HB 2314 (99) Health; Certificate of Public Need (Box 21, Folder 17)
- HB 2315 (99) Dissemination of Criminal History Record Information (Box 21, Folder 18)
- HB 2318 (99) Educational Institution Water Quality Improvement Fund (Box 21, Folder 19)
- HB 2321 (99) Family Involvement in Technology (FIT) Program (Box 21, Folder 20)
- HB 2322 (99) Cruelty to Animals (Box 21, Folder 21)
- HB 2323 (99) Buying, Selling, and Possessing Dog or Cat Fur (Box 21, Folder 22)
- HB 2324 (99) Special Use Permits for Certain Residential Uses (Box 21, Folder 23)
- HB 2331 (99) Virginia Residential Landlord and Tenant Act; Definitions (Box 21, Folder 24)
- HB 2332 (99) Concealed Handgun Permits (Box 21, Folder 25)
- HB 2334 (99) Real Estate Appraiser Board; License Exemptions (Box 21, Folder 26)
- HB 2335 (99) Income Tax; Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation Voluntary Contribution (Box 21, Folder 27)
- HB 2336 (99) Golf Carts (Box 21, Folder 28)
- HB 2337 (99) Health; Sewage System Permits (Box 21, Folder 29)
- HB 2339 (99) Commonwealth Health Research Authority (Box 21, Folder 30)
- HB 2340 (99) Annexation Moratorium (Box 21, Folder 31)
- HB 2341 (99) Prescriptive Authority of Nurse Practitioners and Physician Assistants (Box 21, Folder 32)
- HB 2343 (99) Acceptable Internet Use Policy for State Employees (Box 21, Folder 33)
- HB 2345 (99) Health Insurance; Premium Arrearages (Box 21, Folder 34)
- HB 2348 (99) License Plates (Box 21, Folder 35)
- HB 2350 (99) "Out-of-Services" Inspections (Box 21, Folder 36)
- HB 2354 (99) Health Insurance; Coverage of Certain Pap Smears (Box 21, Folder 37)
- HB 2355 (99) Distribution Cooperatives; Donation of Certain Patronage Capital (Box 21, Folder 38)
- HB 2358 (99) Income Tax; Accessibility Features for the Disabled Tax Credit (Box 21, Folder 39)
- HB 2359 (99) Extensions for Filing (Box 21, Folder 40)
- HB 2360 (99) School Division Participation in Medical Assistance Services (Box 21, Folder 41)
- HB 2365 (99) Workers' Compensation; Volunteer Firefighters (Box 21, Folder 42)
- HB 2366 (99) Not Guilty by Reason of Insanity (Box 21, Folder 43)
- HB 2367 (99) Athletic Trainers; Certification (Box 21, Folder 44)
- HB 2369 (99) Medical Care Facilities Certificate of Public Need (Box 21, Folder 45)
- HB 2370 (99) Historic Rehabilitation Tax Credit (Box 21, Folder 46)
- HB 2373 (99) Extradition (Box 21, Folder 47)
- HB 2378 (99) Parking Violation Notices (Box 21, Folder 48)
- HB 2379 (99) Literary Fund Loans; Legal Opinion Required (Box 21, Folder 49)
- HB 2381 (99) Governor's Development Opportunity Fund (Box 21, Folder 50)
- HB 2384 (99) Compulsory School Attendance; (GED) Testing (Box 21, Folder 50)
- HB 2385 (99) Health Insurance; Requirements for Obstetrical Care Coverage (Box 21, Folder 52)
- HB 2386 (99) Transient Occupancy Tax; Increase in Certain Counties (Box 21, Folder 53)
- HB 2387 (99) Good Time Credits Earned in Jail (Box 21, Folder 54)
- HB 2391 (99) Public Procurement Act; Withdrawal of Bid (Box 21, Folder 55)
- HB 2392 (99) Solicitation of Contributions; Enforcement; Penalties (Box 21, Folder 56)
- HB 2393 (99) Public Procurement Act; Decisions of Public View; Review (Box 21, Folder 57)
- HB 2394 (99) Child Abuse and Neglect; Reporting (Box 21, Folder 58)
- HB 2397 (99) Supplemental Health Insurance Payments for State Retirees (Box 21, Folder 59)
- HB 2401 (99) Estuarine and Coastal System (Box 21, Folder 60)
- HB 2405 (99) Authority to Make Certain Alternative Education Placements (Box 21, Folder 61)
- HB 2407 (99) Child Support; Shared Custody (Box 21, Folder 62)
- HB 2408 (99) Professional Corporations; Transfer of Shares to Charitable Trusts (Box 21, Folder 63)
- HB 2409 (99) Revenue Bonds; Southampton Reception and Classification Center (Box 21, Folder 64)
- HB 2411 (99) Virginia Regional Industrial Facilities Act (Box 21, Folder 65)
- HB 2412 (99) Exemplary Damages for Persons Injured by Intoxicated Drivers (Box 21, Folder 66)
- HB 2413 (99) Workers' Compensation; Cancer Presumption (Box 21, Folder 67)
- HB 2414 (99) Persons with Mental Retardation; Developmental Disabilities (Box 21, Folder 68)
- HB 2415 (99) Gifted Education (Box 21, Folder 69)
- HB 2420 (99) I-64 Weighing Station (Box 21, Folder 70)
- HB 2426 (99) Drug-Free School Zones; School Bus Stops (Box 21, Folder 71)
- HB 2427 (99) Patient Health Records (Box 21, Folder 72)
- HB 2428 (99) Health Professions; Pharmacy (Box 21, Folder 73)
- HB 2430 (99) Regulation of Wastes Transported on Water (Box 21, Folder 74)
- HB 2431 (99) Place for Bringing Action Under a Contract Related to Construction (Box 21, Folder 75)
- HB 2432 (99) Water Facilities Revolving Fund (Box 21, Folder 76)
- HB 2434 (99) Four for Life (Box 21, Folder 77)
- HB 2436 (99) Advance Communications Assistance Fund; Created (Box 21, Folder 78)
- HB 2437 (99) Composition of Board of Visitors of Norfolk State University (Box 21, Folder 79)
- HB 2438 (99) Public Service Companies; Restructuring Utility Companies (Box 21, Folder 80)
- HB 2439 (99) Adult Protective Services (Box 21, Folder 81)
- HB 2441 (99) Corporations; Shareholder Action without Meeting; Prior Notice (Box 21, Folder 82)
- HB 2442 (99) Health Professions; Rehabilitation Providers (Box 21, Folder 83)
- HB 2443 (99) Regulated Land-Disturbing Activities (Box 21, Folder 84)
- HB 2445 (99) Battery of a Teacher (Box 21, Folder 85)
- HB 2450 (99) Robert S. Hornsby Memorial Bridge (Box 21, Folder 86)
- HB 2451 (99) Enforcement of Deeds of Trust (Box 21, Folder 87)
- HB 2452 (99) Patient's Health Records (Box 21, Folder 88)
- HB 2455 (99) Water and Waste Authorities Act; Exempt from Utility Facilities Act (Box 21, Folder 89)
- HB 2460 (99) Investment Partnership Act; created (Box 21, Folder 90)
- HB 2461 (99) Automated Drug Dispensing Systems (Box 21, Folder 91)
- HB 2462 (99) Building Code Violations (Box 21, Folder 92)
- HB 2463 (99) Health Insurance; Small Employer Market Provisions (Box 21, Folder 93)
- HB 2471 (99) Solid Waste Management and Enforcement (Box 21, Folder 94)
- HB 2474 (99) Service Districts (Box 21, Folder 95)
- HB 2475 (99) Identity of Lottery Winners (Box 21, Folder 96)
- HB 2476 (99) Agricultural Education; Coordinators (Box 22, Folder 1)
- HB 2477 (99) Standards of Quality (Box 22, Folder 2)
- HB 2478 (99) Indoor Air Quality in Public Schools (Box 22, Folder 3)
- HB 2480 (99) Educational Opportunities (Box 22, Folder 4)
- HB 2482 (99) Post-Secondary Education; Multi-State Compacts (Box 22, Folder 5)
- HB 2483 (99) Drivers' Licenses and Learner's Permits; Parental Waivers (Box 22, Folder 6)